leadforce1.com 2011-03-15

# Privacy Policy

We help marketers better target their audience and avoid pricing models designed to increase the volume of communications. While MarketForceOne's (MarketForceOne Inc. owns LeadFormix) solutions are focused on improving marketing results and lowering costs, we are also reducing unwanted email, phone, and postal communications by as much as 50%.

Email Campaigns is a product of MarketForceOne, Inc. This Privacy Policy includes activity related to MarketForceOne, including, without limitation, its products LeadFormix and Email Campaigns.

**Anti-Abuse**

If you suspect a client of abusing our services, please contact us at [abuse@LeadFormix.com](mailto:abuse@LeadFormix.com) . All complaints are investigated, and you will receive a response detailing the action that we will take to resolve the issue.

**This policy describes how LeadFormix and Email Campaigns uses and protects your personal information.**

**Scope**

This privacy policy describes how we handle the personal information that you supply to us or concerning your use of our services available through [www.LeadFormix.com,](http://www.leadformix.com/index.php) or any MarketForceOne Inc. web sites including the Email Campaigns product and applies generally to any affiliated web sites (the "Sites"). By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is effective on September 5, 2008 for any current users, and upon acceptance for all new users.

**Collection**

You can browse the Sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are no longer anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to our servers located in the United States.

We may collect and store the following personal information:

  * Email address(es), physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card related information;
  * Transactional information based on your activities on the Sites (such as purchases you make, purchase content, and searches conducted, as they relate to your account or purchases);
  * Billing and other information you provide or is provided on your behalf by a third party;
  * Correspondence through the Sites, and correspondence sent to us;
  * Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Sites, and ad data, other information, including IP address and standard Web log information; and supplemental information from third parties.

**Marketing**

We don't sell or rent the personal information we collect from your using our Sites to third parties for their marketing purposes without your consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies (such as demographic data) to improve and personalize our services. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us, simply "unsubscribe" located at the end of any marketing communication.

**Use of Information**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to:

  * Provide the services and customer support you request;
  * Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;
  * Customize, measure, and improve our services and the Sites’ content and layout;
  * Share service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences;
  * Our Disclosure of Your Information
  * We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety.
  * We may also share your personal information with:
  * Employees and agents of MarketForceOne Inc. in order to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts;
  * Service providers under contract with us who help with our business operations;
  * Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information;
  * Those serving subpoenas;
  * Other business entities, should we plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity.

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy we will not otherwise disclose your personal information without your consent except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

#### Email Campaigns - Responding to Unsolicited Email Complaints

If a complaint is received regarding unsolicited emails being sent from Email Campaigns, an immediate investigation is undertaken by us. The following are our standard responses to complaints:

Initial Warning - The user of Email Campaigns is first notified that an unsolicited email complaint has been lodged against them and: (a) Reminded of the terms they previously accepted. (b) Reminded that the complainant's email address will automatically be flagged for suppression if the complainant did unsubscribe. (c) Requested to manually remove the complainant's email address from their subscriber list if the address was not automatically suppressed because the complainant did not unsubscribe.

Follow-up Warning - If the complainant persists, or if there are multiple complaints, a second warning is issued. The user is again reminded of the terms they previously accepted. Additionally, the user is advised that if they are unable to abide by these terms, they should discontinue using Email Campaigns.

Final Notice - If notifications of unsolicited emails continue and remain unaddressed after the follow-up warning, the user's account privileges will be suspended and eventually terminated.

**Email Campaigns – Prohibited Content**

Do not use Email Campaigns to send anything offensive, to promote anything illegal, or to harass anyone.

  * No Pornography
  * No campaigns selling illegal substances
  * No campaigns that violate the FTC's CAN-SPAM Law

Also, there are some industries that send certain types of content that result in higher than normal bounce rates and abuse complaints, which in turn jeopardizes the deliverability of our entire system. No offense intended, but because we must ensure the highest delivery rates possible for all our customers, we do not allow businesses that offer these types of services, products, or content:

  * Illegal goods or services
  * Escort and dating services
  * Pharmaceutical products
  * Get-rich-quick or work-at-home schemes
  * Online trading, day trading tips, or stock market related content
  * Gambling services or products
  * Multi-level marketing
  * Affiliate marketing
  * Credit repair, get-out-of-debt content
  * Mortgages

Generally speaking, if you're in an industry that is frequently associated with spam, we make no judgments about your line of business, but we cannot afford to risk our deliverability. You will most likely need to look into setting up your own mail servers.

**Bulk or Commercial E-Mail**

User agrees to comply with the regulations as prescribed under the CAN- SPAM Act. User agrees to not send unsolicited email to people other than:

1) Individuals who have signed on to receive this communication and have indicated their consent by providing their email address

2) Individuals who have shown interest in the product

3) Individuals with whom the user is having existing business

User also agrees to have in place a system to unsubscribe or opt out so that any individual who wants to discontinue receiving emails, can do so. User will have unsubscribe options in every email and mention the timeframe by which the individual will stop receiving emails. User must have a privacy policy describing the use of the collected data (like email) and also a way to handle abuse and complaints.

We also reserve the right to unsubscribe individuals if they flag an email as Spam. User also agrees to cooperate with LeadFormix in case there is an abuse complaint and User will provide documentation to determine the consent for sending the emails.

**Email bounce**

LeadFormix will provide reports on the deliverability of email campaigns. The user is expected to go through the results and if there are too many hard bounces (non-existent or unavailable email addresses), LeadFormix may block certain campaigns if they are found to have a high proportion of bounces to prevent loss of reputation of the service. The hard bounced emails need to be removed from the system to improve the deliverability.

**Copyright content**

User agrees not to send emails that contain

  * Material that is proprietary and is not permitted for the user to copy or distribute
  * Material that may be defamatory, threatening, malicious code (viruses, Trojans) and is violating any privacy or proprietary rights
  * Send cContent which may be construed to be deceitful and deliberately inaccurate and/or falsified information
  * LeadFormix reserves the right to terminate the contracts of offenders.

**Cookies**

We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain pages of the Sites to help analyze our Web page flow, customize our services, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. We use cookies to provide services to you.

A few important things you should know about cookies are that:

  * We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.
  * Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session.
  * You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Sites.

**Cookies allow:**

  * You to enter your password less frequently during your use of our Sites.
  * Us to provide information that is targeted to your interests.
  * Us to promote and enforce trust and safety.
  * Us to offer certain features that are only available through the use of cookies.
  * Us to measure promotional effectiveness.

Us to analyze our Web page flow.

You are always free to decline cookies if your browser permits. However, if you decline cookies, you may not be able to use certain features on the Sites, and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently while using the Sites.

**Account Protection**

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters and do not disclose your LeadFormix password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify us and change your password.

**Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information**

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by logging into the Sites. Generally, we will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts in order to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our User Agreement, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

**Security**

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use certain tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Phishing**

In order to protect yourself from email that appears to be from LeadFormix, but may be from a disreputable third party, you should never provide any personal information directly in response to an email you believe you have received from us. Rather, you should always close any such email, open your browser, log directly in to the Sites and change, update or modify any such personal information only using our Sites. In the event that you believe that you have received a request for personal information in an email message that is made to appear that it was sent by us, please inform us immediately.

**General**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Site. All amended terms automatically take effect immediately after they are initially posted on the Site.
